&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：要将模块引入语法，要导入它们，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: To bring modules into your syntax, to import them,
有两种主要的导入样式。
there are two major styles of import.
有很多变化，但有两种主要的进口风格。
There's a bunch of variations, but two major styles of import.
一种称为命名导入语法，您可以在第1行中看到它。
One is called the named import syntax which you see on line 1.
我导出了默认函数，所以从技术上讲，它的名称是default from
I exported the default function, so technically its name is default from
外部，然后我决定将默认导入命名为Ask On
the outside, and then I decided to name that default import ask on
第1行，这意味着现在我的顶级导入发生的范围内，
line 1, which means now in my top level scope of where the import happened,
我现在有一个名为Ask的标识符，
I now have an identifier called ask,
它是绑定到模块内的ask函数的引用。
which is reference bound to the ask function inside of the module.
这就是我们所说的Java风格的导入
That's what we sort of referred to as the Java style of import where
import的字面意思是将标识符导入到您的作用域中。
import means literally to import identifiers into your scope.
第二种样式，如您在第7行中看到的，通常称为名称空间
The second style, as you see on line 7, is referred to generally as the namespace
导入，也就是说我想得到整个模块并收集所有
import, which is to say I wanna get this whole module and collect all of
将其内容放到单个名称分隔的变量上，在本例中称为工作坊。
its contents onto a single name spaced variable, in this case called workshop.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以我做进口*作为车间，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So I do import * as workshop,
这称为名称空间导入。
that's called the namespace import.
这是一个不同的思想流派
And that's a different school of thinking,
也就是说，模块就像这些命名空间的东西。
which is that modules are like these namespace things.
我认为这种风格代表了绝大多数模块是如何完成的
I think that style represents the vast majority of how modules have been done in
过去20年的JavaScript。
JavaScript for the last 20 years.
命名的import语法代表了一种新的思想流派。
And the named import syntax represents kinda the new school of thinking.
不是说一个是对的，一个是错的，但是
It's not that one is right and one is wrong, but
它们是思考你如何消费东西的不同方式。
they're different ways of thinking about how you consume stuff.
我当然属于更喜欢导入名称空间的阵营，然后我
I certainly am in the camp that prefers to import a namespace, and then I
有一个叫车间的东西，然后我有另一个东西叫别的东西。
have a thing called workshop, and then I have another thing called something else.
我的大脑就是这样工作的，有些人喜欢有名字的进口，
That's the way my brain works, some people like the named imports,
谢天谢地，两种语法都有。
both syntaxes,thankfully.
他们不会做命名空间导入和
They weren't gonna do the name space import and
然后他们在最后一分钟添加了它
then they added it at the last minute and
我很感激，因为这是我更喜欢的处理方式。
I was so thankful because that's the way that I would prefer to deal with it.
所以这就是你的ES6模块语法，尽管它是，我们并不期待语法
So there's your ES6 module syntax, such as it is, we're not expecting syntactic
改变，但当你在节点土地上使用它时，将会有各种各样的警告。
changes but there will be a variety of caveats when you're using it in node land.
而且因为它将在节点土地上非常流行，你可以期待那些相同的
And because it's gonna be so popular in node land, you can expect that those same
警告可能也会传到您的浏览器JavaScript中。
caveats will probably carry over to your browser JavaScript, as well.
你有问题。
You got a question.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：当你说你更喜欢旧的模块风格时，你的意思是，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: When you say you prefer the old module style you mean,
在一个文件中显示模块模式？
the revealing module pattern in one file?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：该函数在几张幻灯片前包装。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The function wrapped around a couple slides ago.
&gt；&gt；发言人2：谢谢。&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：嗯哼。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Thank you. &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Mm-hm.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：特别是当我要做一个模块的时候，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Specifically when I'm gonna do a module,
我将我的模块公开为UMD样式的模块。
I expose my modules as UMD style modules.
这就是通用模块定义。
That's the universal module definition.
它应该在浏览器、模块加载器和节点之间进行互操作。
It's supposed to kind of inter-operate between browsers, module loaders and node.
这就是我选择的写作格式。
So that's the format I choose to write in.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：那么您是否在您的
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So whether you use a syntactic support in your
定义模块的语言，或者
language to define your modules, or
不管你是选择用老式的揭示模块模式来破解它，
whether you choose to hack it with the old school revealing module pattern,
同样的概念也适用，即您正在将一组行为组织到
the same concept applies, which is that you're organizing a set of behavior into
一个内聚单元，在其中隐藏数据并公开最少必要的API。
a cohesive unit hiding data in it and exposing a minimal necessary API.
这就是你想要得到的设计模式。
That's the design pattern that you wanna get.
然后，就像我说的，这是你可以学到的最重要的事情之一
And then, like I said, it’s one of the most important things that you can learn
关于组织你的JavaScript。
about organizing your JavaScript.
实际上你在里面做什么并不重要。
It actually doesn’t matter what you do on the inside.
如果这是你真正想要的，你可以在内部到处写类
You could write classes all over place on the inside if that’s how you really wanted
去做一些事情，但你仍然想要组织所有的行为
to do stuff, but you're still gonna want to organize all of that behavior
到一个模块中，这样某人就可以将该行为导入到他们的应用程序中并使用它。
into a module, so that somebody can import that behavior into their app and use it.
模块模式，肯定会留在这里，它不会去任何地方。
Module pattern, is definitely here to stay, it's not gonna go anywhere.
好的，就是这样，这就是模块模式。
All right, so there you go, there is the module pattern.
有鉴于此，我们现在对
And with that, we now have a full breadth of understanding of
词汇范围核心或主要支柱，
the lexical scope core or the main pillar,
这是JavaScript语言的主要支柱。
this main pillar of the JavaScript language.
如果我要归结为三根支柱，这一根是最重要的。
And if I were to boil down among the three pillars, this one is the most important.
这是一个以这样一种基本的方式接触到其他一切的人。
It's the one that touches everything else in such a foundational way.
所以希望这为你提供了一个关于词汇技能的更好的视角。
So hopefully that has provided you a better perspective on lexical skill.